let's talk Trump's brilliant Secretary
of Education Betsy DeVos I love her
she's fun bubbly and she gets the job
done like a human wine
spritzer Betsy is a Visionary in the
field of education and was the first and
only Cabinet member to suggest that
schools needed guns to prevent grizzly
bear
attacks you laugh but I had to pull my
kids out of school when I realized their
social studies teacher was a grizzly
bear
it's the salmon breath that gave him
away now Betsy is the best that's why I
was disgusted to see the mainstream
media whip out their claws and try to
tear her down education secretary Betsy
DeVos was featured on 60 Minutes last
night where she seemed to struggle her
interview last night on 60 Minutes was
very rough she gave a performance that
has not received Stella reviews okay
Stella reviews she got some bad reviews
whatever just like my all male rebuttal
to The Vagina Monologues all right
[Applause]
yeah people can be mean you move
on what really pisses me off is this
gotcha journalism that 60 minutes emplo
if you're not familiar 60 Minutes is a
hidden camera prank show
where Leslie stall their Ashton Kutcher
ambushes unsuspecting interviewees with
a series of meticulously researched
questions listen to stall go for the
jugular why have you become
people say the most hated cabinet
secretary I'm not so sure how exactly
that
happened but I think there are a lot of
really powerful forces Allied against
change does it hurt some sometimes it
does sometimes it does again I think I
think um I'm more misunderstood than
anything yes exactly she's misunderstood
like Dave Matthews lyrics
or anything Matt Damon says about
women there are powerful forces out
there working against AOSS like the
results of things she's done in the past
now people think that just because she
rolled back protections on student loans
that she doesn't like students or that
because she's shifting money from public
schools to private religious and charter
schools that she doesn't like public
education wrong she wants public schools
to thrive that's why she's challenging
them with every conceivable obstacle
it's the same reason I hired that
grizzly bear to come tutor my kids at
home but now here comes lesie stall
totally ambushing Betsy with basic
questions about her job look do you
think that teachers should have guns in
the class room that should be an option
for States and communities to consider
and um I I I hesitate to think of like
my first grade teacher Mrs zor Hoff I
couldn't ever imagine her right um
having a guy and uh being trained in
that way a damn it
Betsy don't bring up an example that
totally undercuts your entire
argument what about your second grade
teacher Mrs reinolds that cold blooded
ice queen could drop a gazelle at 200
yards look dasas is obviously an expert
on schools and she must know everything
about public schools or she would have
spent some time in them have you seen
the really bad schools
maybe try to figure out what what
they're doing I have not I have not I
not intentionally visited schools that
are underperforming maybe you should
maybe I should oh
yes this is worse than I thought uh
Leslie stall isn't just an ambush
journalist she's using Jedi Mind Tricks
maybe you should go to the schools yes
maybe I should go to the schools it's a
trap Betsy the only good time to just
repeat something back is when you're
chanting at a rally or blindly going
along with a marriage that's
it this interview is obviously a massive
failure it's chaotic it's falling apart
and nobody wants to be there it's the
public school of
interviews and Betsy knows that the best
way to fix a public school is to not fix
it and get the hell out of out of there
[Music]